(Bernadette:)me and Howard to have dinner
with her and Leonard?
(Penny:)Oh, that's nice.
(Amy:)No, it's not.
It's a strategic maneuver.
(Amy:)Leonard's new girlfriend is
testing Bernadette's loyalty
(Amy:)to you and the group.
(Amy:)That bitch is crafty.
- You think?
- Of course.
(Amy:)How does the cheetah attack
a herd of wildebeests?
(Amy:)By going after
its weakest member.
(Bernadette:)Well, what makes me
the weakest member?
(Amy:)Your trusting nature coupled
with your teeny-tiny body.
(Amy:)You wouldn't last a minute
on the Serengeti.
(Penny:)Okay, Amy,
you're being silly.
I'm not concerned about
who hangs out with who.
(Penny:)And I certainly
don't have a problem
(Penny:)with Leonard's new girlfriend
who wears way too much makeup.
(Penny:)Ooh, these are cute.
(Penny:)Of course if I buy them,
(Penny:)I'll have to rent
my womb out to a gay couple.
(Bernadette:)It doesn't matter. I'm going to
tell her we can't make it.
Oh, no. You have to go.
(Bernadette:)I don't understand.
(Bernadette:)I thought I was
a teeny-tiny wildebeest.